# Carlos Barranco Soto

# Web Developer

barrancocarlos

in carlosbarrancosoto

### **Summary**

Web Developer with more than 6 years of experience and collaboration in more than 30 Full Stack projects using various technologies.

Experienced in the planning and development of web and hybrid mobile applications using Phyton with the Django Framework, and the Node js stack: Express. js, MongoDb, Angular and React, with modern design and emphasis on aesthetics and user experience.

Efficient in time management, teamwork, and meeting the customer needs. Avid reader, constantly learning new skills, motivated to learn new technologies and languages, good researcher.

#### Skills

Python:

Django (2 years)
Django Rest
Framework (2 years)

BD: PostgreSQL, MySQL

Javascript:

Express.js (2 years) React (2 years) Angular(2 years) BD: MongoDB Web Design:

Html/CSS (7 years) Bootstrap (6 years) Wordpress (6 years) Photoshop (7 years)

## Languages

English: Advanced Portuguese: Intermediate French: Intermediate Spanish: Native

Experience

Freelance Web Developer

Full-Stack Developer

2018 - Present

Brazil

Remote work for companies and professionals in countries like United States, Panama and Colombia building websites and applications. Some important projects:

Bliss Group: Progressive Web App for Wellness Coach. Online courses and workshops. Django, React, Ionic, PostgreSQL. USA 2021.

Arc BonusBook: HRM system for oilfield and gas process equipment company. Django, Angular 5, PostgreSQL. USA 2020.

Expo: Event Management App. Ticket purchase for conferences. Express.js, Angular and MongoDb. Colombia 2019.

Decktra C.A. 2013 - 2017 Venezuela

Co-founder and Developer

Development of corporate websites and applications, custom-built for our clients needs. More than 30 web projects using various technologies. Some important projects:

Mooncrew: Events Website. Users could post concerts and cultural events. Wordpress with Custom Post Types. Australia 2016.

Opordigital: Financial Report System. REsponsive admin panel with HTML, CSS and Jquery with a Zend PHP Framework backend. Venezuela 2015.

2009 - 2014 Universidad Yacambú Venezuela College Professor

Professor at the Department of Audiovisual Communication and Thesis Tutor.

Comunicar C.A. 2004 - 2009 Venezuela **Design Director** 

Wireframes and interfaces desing with Adobe tools. Graphic design for advertising and project management.

#### Education

Engineer's degree, Computer Software. Unicesumar. Brazil. Since 2019.

Master's degree in Audiovisual Communication, Universidad Complutense, Madrid, Spain 2007. Postgraduate degree in Higher Education. UCLA. Venezuela 2014.

Licentiate degree (Summa Cum Laude) in Communication and Media. Universidade Fermin Toro. Venezuela 2004.

#### Other Courses

Online Marketing (Google Digital Garage) 2016.

Introduction to Computer Science. Harvard University (EdX) 2015.

French Course. Alliance Française, Paris, France 2005.

Classical Music. Conservatório Vicente Emilio Sojo. Venezuela 2007.